A Guide to the Wampler Business Records, 1916-1972: SC 0202
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1918-1971
  - Correspondence, November 1964 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, December 1964 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    A.A. Youssef- Ambassador for the United Arab Republic.
  - Correspondence, January 1965 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, February 1965 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    A. Ross Eckler- Acting Director for the Bureau of the Census for the U.S. Department of Commerce.
  - Correspondence, March 1965 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, April 1965 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, May 1965 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, June 1965 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, July 1965 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, August 1965 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, September 1965 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, October 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, November 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, December 1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January-December 1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, February-July 1970 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1971 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, May 1971 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, June 1971 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1971 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    October 11, 1971 letter to Dr. G. Wayne Glick, President of Keuka College in response to a recent article in the Messenger. Wampler comments on the current political situation, the Vietnam War, and activism by the younger generation. Of particular interest are Wampler's comments concerning African Americans. He writes: "when our negroes find out that they can go where they please and do what they please the same as white people, I believe that they will gradually learn that they themselves are mainly responsible for being backward, will quit trying to stir up hate for the white people and be thankful for the good that the white people have done them." He continues, "Also, when the negro women gain more respect for themselves there will probably be less mixing of the races than ever before, which I think will be a good thing, since many of our most militant and trouble making negroes are really white men with little negro blood in them."
  - Correspondence, November 1971 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, December 1971 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, January 1972 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    United States Senate, and the American Biographical Institute.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Letter to the Selective Service Board.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration: Division of Animal Industry.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Series 3: Date Books, 1939-1965
  Series 3: Date Books, 1939-1965, consist of date books signed by Charles W. Wampler Jr. which include personal appointments, business schedules, and notes on farm production.
  - Poult date book, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Provides a list of dates, purchase and costs primarily made during 1939 with a few from 1940. Purchases include "Hatching Bill," "Eggs Booked," "Eggs Bought," "National Turkey Federation Contributions" and others.
  - Pocket ledger, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    The bulk of this ledger appear to be sales records from 1949 with a few in 1950.
  - Year book, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    The user of this date book was Charles Wampler Jr. Included in the date book is a promotional 1949 calendar from Woodward and Lothrop, Washington D.C.
  - Day book, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    The user of this date book was Charles Wampler Jr.
  - Business diaries, 1952-1953, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    The user of these diaries was Charles Wampler Jr.
  - Notebook of farm animals and corresponding information, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Animals are broken down by the owning farm.
- Series 4: Farm Ledgers, 1932-1951
  Series 4: Farm Ledgers, 1932-1951, contains information on the day-to-day operations of the Wampler properties. Some ledgers specify: Ralston Farm, Dry River, Sunny Slope Farm, Glendale Farm, and Blossom Farm. Other ledgers do not specify property names but do contain information such as expenses, account information, flock details, and livestock weights. Items are arranged chronologically.
  - Day-to-day operations, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Contains information such as expenses, cost of turkeys and poults, turkey feed, and the amount for certain goods such as corn meal, ground oats, milk, salt, wheat, and barley.
  - Turkey orders, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Lists the names of the individuals who purchased the turkeys, where they are from, whether purchased hens or toms, how they paid, and how much they spent.
  - Day-to-day operations, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Contains information such as Grain, Oil Mill, Dairy, Cotton Oil, and Feed Service Companies, amounts of turkeys sold and their prices, eggs sold, and the profits and losses from his sales to certain individuals listed.
  - Building hatchery, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Contains information regarding the necessary equipment needed to build the hatchery such as stone, cement, sand, lumber, tile, nails, paint, screws, nails, plaster, as well as the amounts of these goods purchased and their prices, the names of the individuals who provided Wampler with labor and what they were paid, as well as information regarding day to day operations regarding sales.
  - Ralston, Sunny Slope, and Blosser Farm, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Contains information regarding day to day operations, income, expenses, inventory, and the names of people with whom Wampler did business.
  - Sunny Slope, Glendale, and Blosser Farm, 1937-1938 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Contains information regarding day to day operations, income, expenses, and inventory.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, and Dry River Farm, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Contains information regarding day to day operations, income, expenses, inventory, and total expenses for individuals who owe money.
  - Sunny Slope Farm, Eggs Booked, and Poults Booked, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Contains information regarding day to day operations, income, expenses, and inventory at Sunny Slope Farm, as well as the types of poults and eggs purchased, total amounts, dates, and costs.
  - Turkey Laying Flocks, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Contains information regarding the amount of eggs being laid at each of the Wamplers' farms, total income from those eggs, and expenses.
  - Sunny Slope Farm, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Contains information regarding day to day operations, income, regular expenses, special expenses, inventory, and total expenses for individuals who owe money.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, and Huffman Farm, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Contains information regarding eggs and poults, donations, rent, dues, notes, dividends, expenses, insurance, and a brief section on his Colorado Ranch.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, and Huffman Farm, 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Contains information regarding eggs and poults, donations, rent, dues, notes, dividends, expenses, insurance, loans, gravel expenses, Sunny Slope Hatchery expenses, membership and dues for organizations, and a brief section on his Colorado Ranch.
  - Sunny Slope, Glendale, Pine Ridge, and Huffman Farm, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Contains information regarding eggs and poults, rent, dues, expenses, insurance, traveling expenses, Sunny Slope Hatchery, and a brief section on his Colorado Ranch.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, Huffman, Pine Ridge, Colorado, and Wampler-Bowman Farm., 1946 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Contains information regarding eggs, poults, rent, donations, membership dues, dividends, personal loans, travel expenses, taxes, and the income and expenses of the Trap Nest House.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, Huffman, Pine Ridge, and Colorado Farm, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Contains information regarding eggs, poults, donations, bank dividends, travel expenses, taxes, and information pertaining to the Wamplers' Dayton property.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, Huffman, and Pine Ridge Farm, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Contains information regarding eggs, poults, Sunny Slope Hatchery, donations, bank dividends, travel expenses, taxes, notes, and a Willow Lane Farm is briefly mentioned.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, Huffman, Pine Ridge, and Colorado Farm, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Contains information regarding eggs, poults, rent, donations, membership dues, bank dividends, travel expenses, taxes, the Trap Nest House, Dayton Property, and the Sunny Slope Hatchery.
  - Sunny Slope, Ralston, Glendale, Huffman, Pine Ridge, Colorado, and Willow Lane Farm, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Contains information regarding eggs, poults, rent, donations, membership dues, bank dividends, travel expenses, taxes, notes, sales, statements, turkey and hen accounts, and the Dayton property.
  - Farm Ledger, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Contains information regarding hens and toms, amount of eggs laid, hatched, raised, found dead, missing, what pen they belong to, and the number of culls.
  - Assorted Farm Ledgers, 1942-1964 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Series 5: Financial Files, 1941-1971
  Series 5: Financial Files, 1941-1971, houses all loose financial documents relating to the Wampler businesses. The majority of the series consists of receipts from shipping, Wampler Feed & Seed, Sunny Slope Farm, travel expenses, and general purchases while the second part of the series contains miscellaneous bank statements, account information, tax documents for state and federal income, business taxes, and some Wampler family business documents.
  - Bank Statements and Receipts, 1928-1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tax Documents, 1942-1961 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Business Financial Documents, 1946-1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - General Sales Receipts, 1940-1953 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - General Sales Receipts, January-July 1954 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - General Sales Receipts, August-December 1954 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - General Sales Receipts, 1955-1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Commonwealth of Virginia: Agency Purchase Order.
  - Travel Receipts, 1942-1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Commonwealth of Virginia: Travel Expense Reimbursement Voucher, United States Department of Agriculture: Administrative Audit Difference Statement.
  - Charles Wampler and Son's Receipts, 1942-1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Employer Member Unit Life Rate Calculation Sheet.
  - Shipping and Transfer Receipts, 1949-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    American Airlines Airway Bill, United Airlines Air Freight Loss or Damage Claim.
  - Sunny Slope Farm and Hatchery, February 1931-April 1955 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Quantity and Pricing of Chicks and Poults.
  - Sunny Slope Farm and Hatchery, May 1955-December 1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - American-International Charolais Association Receipts, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Balance Statements.
  - Virginia Angus Association Receipts, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Determined Expenses.
  - Contracts, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Purebred Breeding Contract.
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Receipts, 1934-1953 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Feed and Seed Order Information.
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Receipts, January-June 1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Receipts, July-August 1954 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Receipts, September-October 1954 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Receipts, November 1954-May 1964 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Series 6: Philanthropic and Professional Organizations, 1939-1971
  Series 6: Philanthropic and Professional Organizations, 1939-1971, consists of memoranda, meeting minutes, summaries, and administrative information for various organizations with which Charles Wampler Sr. and Jr. were involved. The series documents local and national organizations, of which agricultural organizations figure prominently. See also materials in Series 10: Reports and Studies for philanthropic reports relating to the Bridgewater College Board of Trustees, Virginia Tech Board of Visitors and Children's Home Society of Virginia.
  - Bridgewater College, 1941-1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Bridgewater College Board of Trustees.
  - Children's Home Society of Virginia, 1941-1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Case Work Report, Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Board of Directors, By-Laws of Children's Home Society of Virginia.
  - Harrisonburg Telephone Company, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Aberdeen Angus Association, 1951-1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Terms and Conditions on Dwarfism, Minutes of Board of Directors Meeting, Report of Operations.
  - Virginia Baby Chick Association, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Beef Cattle Improvement Association, 1955-1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Membership Report.
  - Virginia Broiler Producer Association, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Membership-Finance Committee.
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1942-1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    The Department of Agriculture's Contribution to the War Effort, Newcastle Disease in Poultry, Proposed Regional Diagnostic Laboratories, Japanese Beetle Quarantine, State Lime Grinding Plants, Minutes of the Meeting of the State Board of Agriculture and Immigration.
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, 1954-1962 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Confidential Reports of Visits to Corporations, Minutes of Regular Annual Meetings, Financial Statements, and Operating Accounts.
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Board of Visitors, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Virginia State Poultry Federation, 1945-1951 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Minutes of Poultry Federation Directors Meetings, Producer Membership Report, Turkey Membership Report, and Plans and Objectives.
  - Virginia State Poultry Federation Sections 1 - 4, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Names and Addresses, Minutes of Board Meetings, Executive Committee, and Financial Reports.
  - Virginia State Poultry Federation Sections 5 - 12, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Finance Committee, Membership Summaries, Membership Committee, VPI Committee, Taxation Committee, Advertising Committee, Grading and Inspection Committee, and Legislative Action Committee.
  - Virginia State Poultry Federation Sections 13 - 16, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Convention Committee, Insurance Committee, Other Committees, and Miscellaneous.
  - Virginia State Poultry Federation, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Membership Summary, Producer Membership Plan, Financial Condition, Income and Expenses, Preliminary Reports, Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, and Convention Committee Report.
  - Virginia State Turkey Association, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Minutes of the Meeting of the Merchandising Committee.
  - United World Federalists of Virginia, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Minutes of Charlottesville Conference.
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company, Inc., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Minutes of the Board of Directors Meeting of Wampler Feed and Seed Company, Inc.
  - American Cheviot Sheep Society, 1958-1970 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Proposals made by the By-Laws Committee.
  - American-International Charolais Association, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Reciprocity of Information, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Committee for the Defense Saving Program, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Florida Brethren Homes Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - National Advisory Committee on Research, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - National Poultry Defense Committee, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey Turkey Growers' Cooperative Association, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - National Turkey Federation, 1942-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Poultry and Egg National Board, 1940-1943 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - United Wool Growers' Association, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - The State Board of Agriculture and Immigration, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - VPI Alumni Association, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Performance Registry International, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Brethren's General Mission Board, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Christian Record Braille Foundation, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Valley Processors, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Heifer Project, Inc., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - International Baby Chick Association, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - American Angus Association, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Youth Argosy, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Virginia War Savings Staff, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Defense Savings Staff, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - The American Forestry Association, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - War Memorial Association, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Illinois Poultry Improvement Program, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Rural Churchman's Seminar, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Series 7: Photographs, 1939-1971
  Series 7: Photographs, 1939-1971, contains livestock pictures from the Wampler Farms and from farmers across the country with letters attached regarding breeding opportunities and purchase requests. Several personal photographs of the Wampler children are included here.
  - Portraits, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - 01.01 Charles W. Wampler Jr., undated
    - 01.02 William Wampler, undated
    - 01.03 William Wampler (duplicate of 01.02), undated
    - 01.04 William Wampler (duplicate of 01.02), undated
    - 01.05 William Wampler (duplicate of 01.02), undated
    - 01.06 William Wampler (duplicate of 01.02), undated
    - 01.07 William Wampler (duplicate of 01.02), undated
    - 01.08 William Wampler (duplicate of 01.02), undated
    - 01.09 William Wampler, undated
  - Wampler family members, 1939-1955, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - 02.01 Elmer Larson, a son-in-law of the Wampler Family showing a sheep, February 1955
      Accompanied by a note that reads: ""My Son in Law Elmer Larson and grand Daughter Pamela." This note likely refers to photographs 02.01-02.04. The photograph also is labeled February 1955 on the side.
    - 02.02 Pamela, a granddaughter in the Wampler Family holding a sheep with a house in the background, February 1955
      The photograph is labeled February 1955.
    - 02.03 Pamela, a granddaughter in the Wampler Family holding a sheep with a car and a house in the background, March 1955
      The photograph is labeled March 1955 on the side.
    - 02.04 Pamela, a granddaughter in the Wampler Family holding a sheep with a house in the background, June 1955
      The photograph is labeled June 1955 on the side.
    - 02.05 Possibly Charles Wampler Sr. or Jr., holding a sheep near a fence with cloth draped over it, undated
    - 02.06 Possibly Charles Wampler Sr. or Jr., holding a sheep by the head near a pine tree, undated
    - 02.07 Possibly Charles Wampler Sr. or Jr., holding a sheep by the head near a fence with cloth, undated
    - 02.08 Charles Wampler Sr. and unidentified man standing in a field, undated
    - 02.09 William Wampler collecting and examining eggs, undated
    - 02.10 Unidentified boy standing with a leashed cow in a field, undated
    - 02.11 Unidentified girl holding a leashed cow in a field, undated
  - Sheep, 1947-1956 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - 03.01 Sheep in an indoor pen, undated
    - 03.02 Sheep in a pen near a barn, undated
      Caption on back reads: "Yearling stud ram at Normandin– N.C. Cheviot. Beautiful to behold, and a show winner- but no good at all as a breeder. Both he and his lambs have now been culled.
    - 03.03 Sheep in front of a barn, 1955
      Caption on the back refers to North Country Cheviot ewes.
    - 03.04 Flock of sheep in front of a barn, October 1955
      Caption on the back refers to North Country ram lambs.
    - 03.05 Flock of sheep in a field by a farmhouse, May 1948
      Caption on the back reads: "May 1948 Erdenheim Farms of Chestnut Hill Phil 18 Pa."
    - 03.06 Flock of sheep in a field, May 1948
    - 03.07 Man holding a sheep's head, 1949
      Caption on the back reads: "Ch. Cheviot Ewe. Slack Brothers Quebec 1949."
    - 03.08 Man holding a sheep's head, 1949
      Caption on the back reads: "Champion Shropshire Ewe, Slack Brothers, Quebec 1949."
    - 03.09 Flock of sheep in a pen, undated
      Captioned: "11 Mo old Ewe Lambs 'Montadale'."
    - 03.10 Three sheep, 1948
      Caption on the back reads: "4 year old ram on left, 2 ram lambs, HS. Dean flock of 48."
    - 03.11 Flock of sheep, 1948
      Caption on the back reads: "2-2 yr old ewes, 2-2yr. old ewes, 2- ewe lambs, H.S. Dean flock of 48."
    - 03.12 Four sheep near a fence, undated
      Caption on the back reads: "Cheviot and Leicester yearlings."
    - 03.13 Two sheep near a fence, undated
      Caption on the back reads: "Leicester and Cheviot yearlings."
    - 03.14 Five men in front of a fence holding sheep, October 17, 1947
      Caption on the back reads: "Yearling Ewes, Rifle Ranges, Ottawa Photo: Oct. 17th, 1947. Left to right: Cheviot x Leicester, Leicester x Oxford, Leicester x Shropshire, Oxford x Shropshire, Leicester x Cheviot."
    - 03.15 Flock of sheep in a snowy field, February 1955
      Accompanied by a note that reads: "My flock of 170 Ewes." Note also refers to photograph 03.16.
    - 03.16 Unidentified man with a flock of sheep in front of a house, February 1955
  - Cows, 1962-1971 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - 04.01 Three calves with a cow, May 1967
      Caption on the back reads: "Born April 29 - 67, Triplets - 1 day old., Weight 2 averaged 40 # each, 1 averaged 50 #, Dam is five years old., Mr. Wampler: I named them Teeny, Tiny and Tot. (Ethel)"
    - 04.02 Bull in a field, with other cows in the distance, May 1967
      Caption on the back reads: "20-708- Age 9 yrs. Wt. 1900 Sire of dam. Purchased from Mr. Charlie Wampler."
    - 04.03 Bull eating in a pasture, with part of another cow on the side, May 1967
      Caption on the back reads: "age- 3 yrs, wt. 1600 Sire of the Triplets purchased from C.A Miller, Keyser, W.VA."
    - 04.04 Bull standing with a lead, April 29, 1962
      Caption on the back reads: "Eileenmere of Snorest 12 " #3197940 04/29/62."
    - 04.05 Bull eating grass in a field, April 29, 1962
      Caption on the back reads: "Eileenmere of Snorest 12" #3197940 04/29/62."
    - 04.06 Bull standing, April 29, 1962
    - 04.07 Bull standing by a fence, undated